(This story is entirely fictional)
It's all for yourself!
Can't you listen to me just once?
Can't you try to understand me?
(Based on the novel
Doctor Qin: Executer)
Xiaoya...
Xiaoya?
(Mr. Zhang, you asked for me?)
Mr. Zhang.
Xiaoya...
She was drunk.
Got worked up.
And fell.
Quick, clean it up.
Got it.
=Doctor Qin: Executer=
=Episode 21=
Who are you?
Come over.
Do it!
Play it.
This is only a small part of the copies.
I was planning
to have you cancel
Xiaoxue's debt.
But now,
for your innocent daughter's sake too,
I want 500k yuan.
500k for Xiaoxue.
In cash.
And stay away from her.
No negotiating.
Hurry up.
Do it!
Sir,
stop the car.
(FAN A 71954)
Drop it there.
One, two, three, lift!
Mr. Zhang.
Come back here.
(Parking Full)
Keep running.
Keep running!
Why'd you stop?
Wen.
Wen...
Wen!
Run...
Watch out for Zhang Xiaodong...
Boss, what about her?
It's fine. Let her watch.
Xia Wen...
Wen...
Come on. Look at me.
Look at me!
Listen.
She's at the end.
I'll give you a chance to live.
Choke her to death. Right now.
Then we'll be in this together.
You hear me?
I can't let you call the cops on me.
So you have to choke her now!
I can't! I can't...
Hand me that.
Look closely.
No!
Choke her!
Right now!
Choke her! Hurry!
Do it!
I can't...
I don't want to...
I don't want to!
Let's end this pain...
Let's end it...
Give her a big hand!
Miss Jin!
Welcome to the team.
Let's go.
How did you find the body?
I was out for a walk
(Police)
when I saw someone lying there.
Do you come here for walks often?
Yeah. I live nearby.
Qin Ming.
The first shot you fired
made me feel truly relieved.
All these years of guilt
have finally eased a little.
The second shot
was my selfish way to confirm
your feelings for me
over the past decade.
Qin Ming.
Thanks for all of it.
Keke!
♪Sunset washes over the old wall♪
♪Milk tea cools on the stone steps♪
♪Sea wind tugs at your sleeve♪
♪Unspoken words just flee and fade♪
♪The marks on the desk
have faded yellow♪
This is the second time
we've held hands.
♪I turned around,
and a gunshot rang out♪
And it might be the last.
♪No one can truly feel another's pain♪
♪The wind is cold,
a fading shadow sways♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪A bullet pierces the spring night♪
♪You sink into the vast crowd♪
♪One gunshot echoes through half a life♪
Qin Ming.
If we could go back to that rooftop,
you'd pull me out of the darkness,
wouldn't you?
Yes.
♪One gunshot echoes through half a life♪
Mr. Dong, you wanted to see me?
Jin Keke will only talk to you.
I'll make an exception
and let you question her.
(Police)
Did you sleep well?
I finally stopped having nightmares.
Officer Qin,
why don't you get some rest?
After all,
you were my hostage all night.
Hostage?
But you never hurt me.
Officer Qin,
where would you like to start?
Was He Guifen's death
planned or an accident?
She wasn't on my revenge list.
I felt sorry for Xu Meng.
So I wanted her to pay up for Xu Meng.
However, He Guifen was so hot-tempered
that she angered herself to death.
I'm your daughter, Xu Meng.
You're Xu Meng?
You're not Xu Meng.
Who are you?
What do you want?
What do I want?
I'm collecting Xu Meng's debt.
All these years,
you've been living off
Xu Meng's blood money, right?
When her father died,
as her stepmother,
you took the compensation
and sold her to Zhang Xiaodong.
You've been bleeding her dry.
Don't you feel any guilt?
Nonsense!
What on earth do you want?
Should I spell out
every cut you got
from Zhang Xiaodong?
I've traced every kickback you took
for pimping Xu Meng out
to those bosses.
You... you jerk!
Oh, Ms. He,
I should warn you.
You need to pack up and move.
The bank will be taking your house soon.
You... you liar!
Pay me back!
I'm calling the police.
I'll have you all arrested!
Oh, right.
I've transferred the money.
And that contract was fake too.
You'll lose everything.
Enjoy your later years,
if you have any left.
Xu Meng said
she had nightmares too.
Because
she'd also witnessed
Zhang Xiaoya's death.
We are sparrows trapped in a cage.
Xia Wen...
She's the hunter
who saved us with her life.
So for ten years,
I turned myself into a crow.
I'll peck out the eyes of those bad guys
and leave them to rot in the dark.
My weapon is...
their own evil.
♪Sunset washes over the old wall♪
♪Milk tea cools on the stone steps♪
♪Sea wind tugs at your sleeve♪
♪Unspoken words just flee and fade♪
♪The marks on the desk
have faded yellow♪
♪I turned around,
and a gunshot rang out♪
♪No one can truly feel another's pain♪
♪The wind is cold,
a fading shadow sways♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪A bullet pierces the spring night♪
♪You sink into the vast crowd♪
♪Years later, when we meet again♪
♪Don't mention this moonlit night♪
♪The waves smooth
two lines of footprints♪
♪Half a cup of sweetness
sinks into the sand♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪Wind back to shore,
clouds back to hills♪
♪We stop here in this night♪
♪This is the past, the only,
the last look back♪
♪One gunshot echoes through half a life♪